pixpix.co 2016-03-31

# PixPix.co Privacy Policy

## PixPix ("PixPix") operates several websites including PixPix.co. It is PixPix's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

## Website Visitors

Like most website operators, PixPix collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. PixPix's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how PixPix's visitors use its website. From time to time, PixPix may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

## Instagram Content

All photographic and video content on PixPix.co comes from Instagram and was publicly available at the time of its appearing on our site. The content is owned by those who posted it and carries the copyright attributed by that owner. You can control your content's visibility by changing your Instagram settings to prevent your content from appearing on third-party sites like PixPix.co. Visit Instagram's help center to learn more about [controlling your visibility](https://help.instagram.com/116024195217477/).

If you would like to prevent your profile from appearing specifically on PixPix.co, please submit a [removal request](https://pixpix.co/privacy/removal/). For all other inquiries please contact us at [pixgramco@gmail.com](mailto:pixgramco@gmail.com).

## Aggregated Statistics

PixPix may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. PixPix may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, PixPix does not disclose personally-identifying information.

## Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. PixPix uses cookies to help PixPix identify and track visitors, their usage of PixPix website, and their website access preferences. PixPix visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using PixPix's websites, with the drawback that certain features of PixPix's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

## Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by PixPix and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, PixPix may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in PixPix's sole discretion. PixPix encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy.
